

Estiénne Prior

Developer with a mix of skills from both Computer Science and Marketing backgrounds. Key experience with React, TypeScript, Python & AWS; as well as demonstrated results in ecommerce platform management, SEO and social media content creation.

3 Sunbeam Court, Eatons Hill QLD 4037 P: 0449 754 488 E: estieprior@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/estienneprior

EXPERIENCE

DMS Innovations — Full-Stack Developer

NOVEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Full-stack development of ORA DMS, a cloud-deployed SAAS for the automotive industry. In addition to implementing new features, I have been prominently involved in translating the React front-end from JavaScript to TypeScript and improving back-end PostgreSQL database communication.

Brisbane Motorcycles — *Director of IT & Ecommerce*

NOVEMBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2022

As my experience grew, I took on:

- development of in-house technology with Dart, Python &
 JavaScript running on AWS EC2 instances, translating various API
 feeds into a practical lead management experience.
- management of IT infrastructure, intellectual property and AWS deployment of self-hosted 3CX telecommunication.
- Ground-up creation of Riders Market & Sydney City Motorcycles websites + marketing management for both, alongside Brisbane Motorcycles.

Brisbane Motorcycles — *Product Database Manager*

DECEMBER 2020 - NOVEMBER 2021

Regulated product metadata with Python utilising Pandas, Selenium and Cron, in addition to ecommerce web development to ensure a smoother customer experience.

Wesley Mission Queensland — Keeping Connected Team Member

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

During the COVID-19 pandemic, I assisted WMQ with keeping aged care residents connected to their families in unfamiliar times.

EDUCATION

Queensland University of Technology —

Bachelor of IT (Computer Science) / Bachelor of Business (Marketing)

FEBRUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2020

Graduated with a GPA of 5.5 and awarded placement on the Dean's List.

SKILLS

PERN stack experience, including essential TypeScript knowledge.

Proven AWS proficiency of instance deployment, management and optimisation.

Strong Python ability with Pandas, Selenium, Tkinter and API communication.

Full-Stack Flutter
Application Development,
merging data from APIs &
MongoDB into functional user
experiences.

Extensive marketing knowledge of SEO, Google Analytics, Ads & Merchant Centre and content creation for EDM campaigns.

Ecommerce expertise from managing 3 Ecommerce stores, and driving 'Brisbane Motorcycles' monthly online sales from \$60K to \$200K/month.

LANGUAGES & ENVIRONMENTS

Python, Dart, JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, C#, HTML, CSS, SQL, React, MongoDB, Node.js, AWS, Git